<AstroObjectEntry xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
                  xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/shiplog_schema.xsd">
  <ID>Lava Core</ID>
  <Entry>
    <ID>LAVA_CORE_ROOT</ID>
    <Name>Lava Core</Name>

    <RumorFact>
      <ID>LV_DESCRIPTION</ID>
      <SourceID>LH_EXTINCT_VOLCANO_FACT</SourceID>
      <Text>Below the Extinct Volcano, there is a cracked sphere with lava rising and falling.</Text>
    </RumorFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LV_BUTTONS</ID>
      <Text>This core contains structures locked by various buttons. They are very easy to press, not requiring very much pressure to activate, but must all be activated simultaneously.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LV_SIGNAL</ID>
      <Text>A dish at the entrance to the core is sending and receiving communications from various structures on the core.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>

    <Entry>
      <ID>LV_FIRST_BUTTON_FACT</ID>
      <Name>Structure On A Cliff</Name>

      <ExploreFact>
        <ID>LV_FIRST_BUTTON_INFO</ID>
        <Text>I found a locked structure with a button right outside of it. I don't see a second one, could it have fallen into the lava?</Text>
      </ExploreFact>
    </Entry>

    <Entry>
      <ID>LV_SECOND_BUTTON_FACT</ID>
      <Name>Structure By Pillars</Name>

      <ExploreFact>
        <ID>LV_SECOND_BUTTON_INFO</ID>
        <Text>I found a locked structure with two pillars nearby sticking out of the lava.</Text>
      </ExploreFact>
    </Entry>

    <Entry>
      <ID>LV_THIRD_BUTTON_FACT</ID>
      <Name>Old Abandoned Town</Name>

      <ExploreFact>
        <ID>LV_THIRD_BUTTON_INFO</ID>
        <Text>I found a series of locked structures.</Text>
      </ExploreFact>
    </Entry>

    <Entry>
      <ID>LV_SHRINE_FACT</ID>
      <Name>Lava Shrine</Name>

      <RumorFact>
        <ID>LV_SHRINE_INFO</ID>
        <RumorName>Strange Building</RumorName>
        <RumorNamePriority>5</RumorNamePriority>
        <Text>Near the entrance to the lava core exists a very large building. It is not made of metal like the other structures nearby. A barrier prevents entry.</Text>
        <AltText>
          <Text>A shrine can be found a short distance from the entrance to the lava core. A barrier blocks entry, but activating three buttons across the core opens it.</Text>
          <Condition>LV_SHRINE_ENTRY</Condition>
        </AltText>
      </RumorFact>

      <RumorFact>
        <ID>LV_SHRINE_BUTTON_ONE</ID>
        <SourceID>LV_FIRST_BUTTON_FACT</SourceID>
        <RumorName>Button's Response</RumorName>
        <RumorNamePriority>0</RumorNamePriority>
        <Text>I found a button at the Structure on a Cliff.</Text>
      </RumorFact>

      <RumorFact>
        <ID>LV_SHRINE_BUTTON_TWO</ID>
        <SourceID>LV_SECOND_BUTTON_FACT</SourceID>
        <RumorName>Button's Response</RumorName>
        <RumorNamePriority>1</RumorNamePriority>
        <Text>I found a button at the Structure by Pillars.</Text>
      </RumorFact>

      <RumorFact>
        <ID>LV_SHRINE_BUTTON_THREE</ID>
        <SourceID>LV_THIRD_BUTTON_FACT</SourceID>
        <RumorName>Button's Response</RumorName>
        <RumorNamePriority>2</RumorNamePriority>
        <Text>I found a button at the Old Abandoned Town.</Text>
      </RumorFact>

      <ExploreFact>
        <ID>LV_SHRINE_ENTRY</ID>
        <Text>When I entered the shrine, I fell through a fake floor! It turns out that the inhabitants have walls that appear to exist, but are not at all solid. The only way to tell that wall is fake is a symbol on it, which could be <![CDATA[<color=FF6E2B>hidden in plain sight</color>]]>.</Text>
      </ExploreFact>

      <ExploreFact>
        <ID>LV_SHRINE_MURALS</ID>
        <Text>At the end of the shrine, I found four murals. The first three seem to depict several planets becoming increasingly unstable and falling apart. The fourth depicts a group flying away in a ship, while another group is saddened and angered at being left behind.</Text>
      </ExploreFact>
    </Entry>
  </Entry>
  
  
</AstroObjectEntry>