<AstroObjectEntry xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
                  xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/shiplog_schema.xsd">
  <ID>Lonely Hermit</ID>
  <Entry>
    <ID>LONELY_HERMIT_ROOT</ID>
    <Name>Lonely Hermit</Name>

    <RumorFact>
      <ID>LH_ARRIVAL</ID>
      <RumorName>Dusty Planet</RumorName>
      <Text>I've arrived in Hearth's Neighbor. The only immediately obvious feature in this system is a lone, dusty planet.</Text>
    </RumorFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LH_INFO</ID>
      <Text>Hearth's Neighbor's sole planet. The surface is devoid of life.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LH_ELEVATOR</ID>
      <Text>I found some kind of elevator that went below the surface and emerged in a strange expansive area. Is this planet <![CDATA[<color=FF6E2B>bigger on the inside?</color>]]>?</Text>
    </ExploreFact>
  </Entry>

  <Entry>
    <ID>LH_POWER_PLANT_FACT</ID>
    <Name>Ghost Matter Structure</Name>

    <RumorFact>
      <ID>LH_PLANT_RUMOR</ID>
      <SourceID>LONELY_HERMIT_ROOT</SourceID>
      <RumorName>Domed Structure</RumorName>
      <Text>There is a strange domed structure on the surface of Lonely Hermit.</Text>
    </RumorFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LH_PLANT_NO_ENTRY</ID>
      <Text>There does not seem to be a way inside. Judging by the copious amounts of Ghost Matter leaking out of it, it may not be a good idea to go inside it regardless.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LH_PLANT_INFO</ID>
      <Text>A mural indicates that this structure is built around a comet that once crashed into the planet. The planet's inhabitants harnessed a power from within the comet to fuel their civilization.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>
  </Entry>

  <Entry>
    <ID>LH_NORTHERN_WASTELAND_FACT</ID>
    <Name>Northern Wasteland</Name>

    <RumorFact>
      <ID>LH_WASTELAND_RUMOR</ID>
      <SourceID>LONELY_HERMIT_ROOT</SourceID>
      <RumorName>North Pole</RumorName>
      <Text>There appears to be some snow-covered mountains at the north pole.</Text>
      <AltText>
        <Text>At the north pole, there are small remnants of civilization.</Text>
        <Condition>LH_WASTELAND_ELEVATOR</Condition>
      </AltText>
    </RumorFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LH_WASTELAND_ELEVATOR</ID>
      <Text>I found a functioning elevator in the wasteland.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>
  </Entry>

  <Entry>
    <ID>LH_EXTINCT_VOLCANO_FACT</ID>
    <Name>Extinct Volcano</Name>

    <RumorFact>
      <ID>LH_VOLCANO_RUMOR</ID>
      <SourceID>LONELY_HERMIT_ROOT</SourceID>
      <RumorName>Tall Mountain</RumorName>
      <Text>There appears to be a tall, hollow mountain close to the south pole.</Text>
      <AltText>
        <Text>A long-extinct volcano exists on the surface.</Text>
        <Condition>LH_VOLCANO_ELEVATOR</Condition>
      </AltText>
    </RumorFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LH_VOLCANO_ELEVATOR</ID>
      <Text>I found a functioning elevator on a structure within the caldera of the volcano.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>
  </Entry>

  <Entry>
    <ID>LH_DEAD_LAKE_FACT</ID>
    <Name>Dead Lake</Name>

    <RumorFact>
      <ID>LH_LAKE_RUMOR</ID>
      <SourceID>LONELY_HERMIT_ROOT</SourceID>
      <RumorName>Large Structure</RumorName>
      <Text>There is a large structure surrounded by a moat.</Text>
      <AltText>
        <Text>A strange structure exists surrounded by a moat. Despite the water, the area does not have any signs of life.</Text>
        <Condition>LH_LAKE_ELEVATOR</Condition>
      </AltText>
    </RumorFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LH_LAKE_ELEVATOR</ID>
      <Text>I found a functioning elevator within the structure.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LH_LAKE_HANGAR</ID>
      <Text>The structure has some kind of landing/launching pad for larger ships. The pad is connected to a large hangar of some kind where the inhabitants of this planet stored resources to build a much larger structure.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>

    <Entry>
      <ID>LH_LAKE_DOOR_FACT</ID>
      <Name>Satellite Room</Name>

      <RumorFact>
        <ID>LH_LAKE_DOOR</ID>
        <RumorName>Strange Door</RumorName>
        <Text>There is a massive locked door in the hangar.</Text>
      </RumorFact>

      <ExploreFact>
        <ID>LH_LAKE_SATELLITE</ID>
        <Text>Behind the door was a floating satellite pointing at something in space. There is a signal coming out of it.</Text>
      </ExploreFact>
    </Entry>
  </Entry>
  
</AstroObjectEntry>