<AstroObjectEntry xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
                  xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/shiplog_schema.xsd">
  <ID>TIMBER_HEARTH</ID>
  <Entry>
    <ID>HN_MUSEUM_PLATE</ID>
    <Name>Museum Plate</Name>

    <RumorFact>
      <ID>HN_MUSEUM_PLATE_INTRO</ID>
      <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
      <Text>The museum has restored an old exhibit that's been in storage for a while. It can be found behind the stairs.</Text>
      <AltText>
        <Text>The museum has an alien plate on display. While it doesn't seem to be Nomai in origin, its creator is unknown.</Text>
        <Condition>HN_MUSEUM_PLATE_DETAILS</Condition>
      </AltText>
    </RumorFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>HN_MUSEUM_PLATE_DETAILS</ID>
      <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
      <Text>The plate has a map of two solar systems carved on it. One is our system, but the other is a nearby system, Hearth's Neighbor. With a warp drive in one's ship, one could warp to that system and check it out.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>HN_MUSEUM_PLATE_RESOLUTION</ID>
      <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
      <Text>The plate was left by the sole survivor of Hearth's Neighbor's inhabitants. They had crashed onto our planet and lived here until the end of their days.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>
  </Entry>

  <Entry>
    <ID>HN_ESCAPE_POD</ID>
    <Name>Escape Pod</Name>
    
    <RumorFact>
      <ID>HN_POD_RUMOR</ID>
      <SourceID>HN_MUSEUM_PLATE</SourceID>
      <Text>The damage report from the Derelict Ship showed an escape pod land on Timber Hearth. A signal from the ship connected to it.</Text>
    </RumorFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>HN_POD_RESOLUTION</ID>
      <Text>The pod is intact! Whoever landed here survived, though what happened to them is a mystery lost to time. The plate at the museum came from the hull of the pod, likely carved out by the survivor(s) wanting to leave a message of where they came from.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>HN_POD_THANKS</ID>
      <Text>You have finished the Jam version of Hearth's Neighbor! Congrats! Of course, there may still be a few secrets remaining...</Text>
    </ExploreFact>
    
  </Entry>
</AstroObjectEntry>